Guide to the Jerome New Frank Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE & SUBJECTS FILE 1941-1957, Circa May 1941-1957; Series IV; 12' (29 boxes)
  - Correspondence
    - Mueller, Addison A., 1947, 1949, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 637)
    - Muffly, Glenn, 1942 (Box 61, Folder 638)
    - Munson, Halsey, 1951-1953 (Box 61, Folder 639)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 15/9
    - Murphy, Frank, 1945 (Box 61, Folder 640)
    - Nac-Nav, 1941-1951, 1954-1956, undated (Box 61, Folder 641)
    - Ne-Ny, 1941-1954, 1956, undated (Box 62, Folder 642)
    - Nathanson, Jerome., 1944-1946, 1948-1950, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 643)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 18/7
      See also: box 50, folder 204 Conference on Atomic Power and Public Policy
    - Nathanson, Nathaniel L., 1948, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 644)
    - The Nation, 1945, 1947, 1949, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 645)
      See also: box 58, folder 486
    - National Association of Women Lawyers, 1944-1946 (Box 62, Folder 646)
    - National Broadcasting Company, 1946, 1949 (Box 62, Folder 647)
    - National Conference of Bar Examiners, 1943-1946, 1949, 1953, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 648)
    - National Health Assembly, 1948-1949 (Box 62, Folder 649)
    - National Law Student Conference on Legal Education, 1947 (Box 62, Folder 650)
    - National Lawyers Guild, 1942-1946, 1951, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 651)
    - Nebraska, The University of, 1945, 1947, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 652)
    - Needham, Joseph, 1951 (Box 62, Folder 653)
    - Nehemkis, Peter R. Jr., 1941, undated (Box 62, Folder 654)
    - Nelson, Frederic., 1946 (Box 62, Folder 655)
    - Neumann, A. F., 1950 (Box 62, Folder 656)
    - Neumann, Franz L., 1953-1954 (Box 62, Folder 657)
    - Nevins, Allan., 1950-1952 (Box 62, Folder 658)
      See: box 50, folder 197
    - The New Leader, 1951, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 659)
    - The New Republic, 1942, 1946-1948, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 660)
      See also: box 48, folder 112 See also: box 70, folder 881
    - New School for Social Research., 1944-1947, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 661)
      See also: box 64, folder 714 See also: box 69, folder 850 See also: box 57, folder 455
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1945-1949, 1952, 1955-1956 (Box 62, Folder 662)
      See: box 66, folder 766 See: box 54, folder 340 See: box 71, folder 919
    - New York Law School, 1947-1950, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 663)
    - New York Patent Law Association, The, 1941-1948, 1952-1954, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 664)
    - New York Post, 1944-1946; 1949-1950, 1952-1954, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 665)
      See also: box 59, folder 526 See also: box 59, folder 564 See also: box 60, folder 578 See also: box 71, folder 937
    - New York State Bar Association, 1942, 1946-1948, 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 666)
    - New York, The College of the City of, 1941-1942, 1948, 1951, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 667)
    - New York Times, 1942, 1946-1950, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 668)
      See also: box 48, folder 132 See also: box 56, folder 432 See also: box 58, folder 496 See also: box 60, folder 606 See also: box 64, folder 724
    - New York University, 1944, 1948-1949, 1951, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 669)
    - New York University Law Quarterly Review, 1941, 1948-1954, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 670)
    - New York University School of Law, 1948-1949, 1952, 1954, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 671)
    - New York World-Telegram, 1942, 1948-1949 (Box 63, Folder 672)
      See: box 55, folder 387 See: box 56, folder 407 See: box 37, folder 584
    - Nickerson, Eugene, 1946, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 673)
    - Niehbur, Reinhold, undated (Box 63, Folder 674)
    - Niesen, Waldemar A., 1943 (Box 63, Folder 675)
    - Niles, Russell D., 1956 (Box 63, Folder 676)
    - Nims, Harry D., 1944, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 677)
    - Nizer, Louis, 1947, 1949-1950, 1953-1954 (Box 63, Folder 678)
    - Northrup, Filmer S. C., 1952 (Box 63, Folder 679)
    - Northwestern University, 1950-1952 (Box 63, Folder 680)
    - Northwestern University Law Review, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 681)
    - Notre Dame Law School, 1951, 1954-1956 (Box 63, Folder 682)
    - The Notre Dame Lawyer, 1948-1950, 1953-1956 (Box 63, Folder 683)
    - Nydick, A. J., 1947 (Box 63, Folder 684)
    - O, 1941-1942, 1944-1949, 1951, 1953-1956 (Box 63, Folder 685)
    - Oakley, Cletus O., 1954 (Box 63, Folder 686)
    - O'Brien, Robert H., 1941-1943, 1945, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 687)
    - Odium, Floyd B., 1941-1942 (Box 63, Folder 688)
    - O'Dwyer, William, 1946-1948 (Box 63, Folder 689)
    - Ohio State Law Journal, 1949, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 690)
    - Ohio State University, The, College of Law, 1942, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 691)
    - O'Mahoney, Joseph C., 1944 (Box 63, Folder 692)
    - Opffer, Ivan, 1941-1942 (Box 63, Folder 693)
    - Oppenheimer, Franz M., 1945, 1954-1956 (Box 63, Folder 694)
    - Oppenheimer, Monroe, 1941-1942 (Box 63, Folder 695)
    - O'Sullivan, Patrick B., 1942, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 696)
    - Oxford University Press, 1945-1947, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 697)
    - P, 1941-1956, undated (Box 63, Folder 698)
    - Padover, Saul, 1941, 1952, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 699)
    - Palfrey, John G., 1954 (Box 63, Folder 700)
    - Panuch, J. Anthony, 1941, 1944-1945, 1947-1949, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 701)
    - Parker, John J., 1944, 1952-1953, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 702)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 13/7
    - Patterson, Edwin W., 1943-1951, 1953-1954 (Box 64, Folder 703)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 15/16
    - Patterson, Robert P., 1941, 1948-1949, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 704)
    - Paul, Julius, 1955, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 705)
    - Paul, Randolph E., 1941-1943 (Box 64, Folder 706)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 28/14
    - Paul, Randolph E., 1944 (Box 64, Folder 707)
    - Paul, Randolph E., 1945-1956 (Box 64, Folder 708)
    - Paul, Richard H., 1947-1948 (Box 64, Folder 709)
    - Pearson, Drew, 1941, 1944, 1949-1950 (Box 64, Folder 710)
    - Pecora, Ferdinand, 1948-1949, 1951, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 711)
    - Peebles, Don M., 1941, 1946, 1951, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 712)
    - Pegler, Westbrook, 1950 (Box 64, Folder 713)
    - Pekelis, Alexander H., 1941-1946 (Box 64, Folder 714)
    - Pennsylvania Law Review, University of, 1942, 1948-1951, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 715)
    - Pennsylvania Law School, University of, 1948-1949, 1951, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 716)
    - Pepper, Benjamin, 1953 (Box 64, Folder 717)
    - Pepper, George Wharton, 1944, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 718)
    - Perkins, Milo, 1941-1943 (Box 64, Folder 719)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 12/6
    - Perlman, Mark, 1950 (Box 64, Folder 720)
    - Perriaux, Jaime, 1946 (Box 64, Folder 721)
    - Peters, John P., 1953, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 722)
    - Petren, Sture, 1949 (Box 64, Folder 723)
    - Phillips, Cabell, 1946 (Box 64, Folder 724)
    - Phillips, Orie L., 1942-1944 (Box 64, Folder 725)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 32/7
      See also: box 50, folder 191 See also: box 57, folder 452 See also: box 61, folder 628 See also: box 68, folder 816 See also: box 118, folders 1142-1146
    - Phillips, Orie L., 1945-1947, 1949-1950, 1952 (Box 64, Folder 726)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 24/10
    - Philosophy of Science, 1948-1949, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 727)
    - Pickett, Charles, 1948 (Box 65, Folder 728)
    - Pike, James A., 1942 (Box 65, Folder 729)
    - Pike, Sumner T., 1941, 1946-1948, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 730)
    - Pileckas, Joseph J., 1949 (Box 65, Folder 731)
    - Pilley, John, 1946 (Box 65, Folder 732)
    - Pilpel, Harriet F., 1944-1945, 1947-1951, 1953, 1955-1956 (Box 65, Folder 733)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 24/17
    - Pollack, Milton, 1950-1951, 1954, n.d (Box 65, Folder 734)
    - Pollak, Louis H., 1956 (Box 65, Folder 735)
      See also: box 126, folder 1218
    - Posner, Louis S., 1956 (Box 65, Folder 736)
    - Post Office, United States, 1945-1947, 1949-1954 (Box 65, Folder 737)
    - Pound, Roscoe, 1941-1942, 1947 (Box 65, Folder 738)
    - Powell, Thomas Reed, 1942, 1944, undated (Box 65, Folder 739)
    - Practising Law Institute, 1942-1944, 1947, 1950-1951 (Box 65, Folder 740)
    - Prashker, Herbert, 1946 (Box 65, Folder 741)
    - Prashker, Louis, 1947, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 742)
    - Pressman, Lee, 1942, 1945, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 743)
    - Preston, Jerome, 1942 (Box 65, Folder 744)
    - Prettyman, E. Barrett, 1945, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 745)
    - Price, Byron, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 746)
    - Princeton University, 1948-1950 (Box 65, Folder 747)
    - Princeton University Press, 1945, 1948-1956 (Box 65, Folder 748)
    - Programs and Lectures, Inc., 1948-1950 (Box 65, Folder 749)
    - Proskauer, Joseph M., 1942, 1947-1948, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 750)
      See also: box 45, folder 28
    - Public Affairs Institute, 1949-1950, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 751)
    - Purcell, Ganson, 1941-1945, 1951, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 752)
    - Q, 1948, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 753)
    - R, 1941-1956, undated (Box 66, Folder 754)
    - Rabkin, Sol., 1953, 1956, undated (Box 66, Folder 755)
      See also: box 46, folder 45
    - Radin, Max, 1942-1950 (Box 66, Folder 756)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 25/21
    - Rascoe, Burton, 1942 (Box 66, Folder 757)
    - Rasenberger, Raymond J., 1942 (Box 66, Folder 758)
    - Ratner, Sidney, 1952-1953, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 759)
    - Reader's Digest, 1941, 1943, 1945-1946, 1948-1951, 1953-1954, 1956, undated (Box 66, Folder 760)
      See also: box 52, folder 287 See also: box 53, folder 304 See also: box 55, folder 389 See also: Robert Littell box 52, folder 263 See also: box 52, folder 269
    - A Red-White-and-Blue Herring: letters in response to an article written by JNF (1)., 1941-1942 (Box 66, Folder 761)
      See also: box 156, folder 435
    - A Red-White-and-Blue Herring: letters in response to an article written by JNF (2), 1941-1942 (Box 66, Folder 762)
    - A Red-White-and-Blue Herring: letters in response to an article written by JNF (3), 1941-1942 (Box 66, Folder 763)
    - Reed, Stanley, 1942-1944, 1946-1947, 1949, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 764)
    - Reeve, J. E., 1945 (Box 66, Folder 765)
    - Reid, Helen Rogers., 1946-1947 (Box 66, Folder 766)
    - Reinhardt, Justin N., 1941-1943, 1948, 1950, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 767)
    - Reiss, Leo J., 1945, 1950-1951 (Box 66, Folder 768)
    - Resnick, Leo, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 769)
    - Rheinstein, Max, 1942-1943, 1947-1949, 1956-1957 (Box 66, Folder 770)
    - Rice, Elmer, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 771)
    - Richter, B. Nathaniel, 1947, 1949, 1953-1956 (Box 67, Folder 772)
    - Rieff, Philip and Susan, 1954-1955 (Box 67, Folder 773)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 8-2/14
    - Riesman, David and Evelyn, 1948-1952, 1955-1956, undated (Box 67, Folder 774)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 31-2/15
    - Riess, Ernst and Paul H., 1943 (Box 67, Folder 775)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 2-3/0
    - Rifkind, Robert S., 1955 (Box 67, Folder 776)
    - Rifkind, Simon H, 1942-1944, 1947-1950, 1952-1954, undated (Box 67, Folder 777)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 11/10
    - Roberg de Laurentiis, Elena, 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 778)
    - Roberts, Owen J., 1942, 1945 (Box 67, Folder 779)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1941-1942 (Box 67, Folder 780)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, The, 1952, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 781)
    - Rodell, Fred., 1941, 1945, 1947-1950, 1954-1955, undated (Box 67, Folder 782)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 6/16
    - Roehner, Edward T., 1947, 1949, 1951-1952, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 783)
    - Rogers, Will Jr., 1943 (Box 67, Folder 784)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1941-1942 (Box 67, Folder 785)
    - Rose, Stuart, 1941, 1943 (Box 67, Folder 786)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 9/8
    - Rose, William H., 1949 (Box 67, Folder 787)
    - Rosenberg, James N., 1942, 1949 (Box 67, Folder 788)
    - Rosenberg (Julius and Ethel) Affair: public opinion letters, 1952-1953 (Box 67, Folder 789)
    - Rosenblatt, William, 1946, 1948, 1951-1956 (Box 67, Folder 790)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 14/9
    - Rosenfarb, Joseph, 1945-1946, 1948 (Box 67, Folder 791)
    - Rosenthal, Morris S., 1948, 1950, 1952 (Box 67, Folder 792)
    - Rosenwald (Julius) Fund., 1946 (Box 67, Folder 793)
      See also: box 52, folder 280
    - Rosenwald, Lessing J., 1943, 1945-1946, 1948 (Box 67, Folder 794)
      See also: box 45, folders 26-27
    - Ross, Alf, 1950 (Box 67, Folder 795)
    - Rosten, Leo, 1951, 1953, 1955-1956 (Box 67, Folder 796)
    - Rostow, Eugene V., 1947, 1949, 1953, 1955-1956, undated (Box 67, Folder 797)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 12/14
    - Rothschild, George, 1942 (Box 67, Folder 798)
    - Rothschild, Mary (Mrs. Edward I.), 1945, undated (Box 67, Folder 799)
    - Rovere, Richard H., 1946-1950, 1955, undated (Box 67, Folder 800)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 15/21
      See also: box 182, folder 47
    - Rowe, James Jr., 1942-1943 (Box 67, Folder 801)
    - Rubin, Robert S., 1943, 1947 (Box 67, Folder 802)
    - Ruby, Lionel, 1950, undated (Box 67, Folder 803)
    - Ruml, Beardsley, 1942-1943, 1947-1948 (Box 67, Folder 804)
    - Russell, Bertrand, 1944 (Box 67, Folder 805)
    - Rutgers Law Review, 1952, 1954-1955 (Box 67, Folder 806)
    - Rutgers University., 1949, 1952, 1955-1956 (Box 67, Folder 807)
      See also: box 66, folder 759
    - Rutgers University Press., 1952-1953 (Box 67, Folder 808)
    - Rutledge, Wiley, 1945 (Box 67, Folder 809)
    - Rutter, Irvin C., 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 810)
    - Ryan, Sylvester J., 1956 (Box 67, Folder 811)
    - Sa-Sn, 1941-1956, undated (Box 68, Folder 812)
    - So-Sy, 1941-1956 (Box 68, Folder 813)
    - Sachs, Alexander, 1944-1945, 1950 (Box 68, Folder 814)
    - Safford, Truman S., 1942 (Box 68, Folder 815)
    - Sanborn, John B., 1942-1945 (Box 68, Folder 816)
      See also: box 50, folder 191 See also: box 57, folder 452 See also: box 61, folder 628 See also: box 64, folder 725 See also: box 118, folders 1142-1146
    - Saturday Evening Post, 1941-1943, 1946, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 817)
      See also: box 45, folder 11 See also: box 56, folder 143 See also: box 62, folder 655 See also: box 67, folder 786 See also: box 69, folder 860 See also: box 70, folder 880
    - Saturday Review of Literature, 1945-1951, 1953, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 818)
      See also: box 50, folder 198 See also: box 51, folder 219 See also: box 56, folder 403 See also: box 72, folder 961
    - Savage, Royce H., 1952 (Box 68, Folder 819)
    - Saypol, Irving H., 1950, undated (Box 68, Folder 820)
    - Sayre, Paul, 1944-1947, 1952 (Box 68, Folder 821)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 31/18
    - Scanlon, Alfred L., 1950-1953 (Box 68, Folder 822)
      See also: box 63, folder 683
    - Schachner, Bruno., 1948-1949, 1951-1952, 1954-1956, undated (Box 68, Folder 823)
      See also: box 53, folder 301 See also: box 178, folder 1
    - Schlamm, William S., 1943, 1945-1946, 1948 (Box 68, Folder 824)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur Jr., 1947, 1950-1952, 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 825)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 11/13
    - Schmidt, Godfrey P., 1949-1950 (Box 68, Folder 826)
    - Schmulowitz, Nat, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 827)
    - Schulsinger, Gerald G., 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 828)
    - Schultz, Franklin M., 1946, 1949-1951, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 829)
      See also: box 72, folder 974
    - Schwartz, Arthur L., 1946, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 830)
    - Schwartz, Charles P. Jr., 1950, 1953-1954 (Box 68, Folder 831)
    - Schwartz, Dick, 1943, 1948, 1950, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 832)
    - Schwartz, Louis B., 1953-1954 (Box 68, Folder 833)
    - Schwartz, Richard D., 1956 (Box 68, Folder 834)
    - Schwartz, Ulysses S., 1941-1942, 1948-1949, 1953, 1955, undated (Box 68, Folder 835)
    - Scott, John W., 1942-1943 (Box 68, Folder 836)
    - Seagle, William, 1942-1943, 1945-1948, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 837)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 29/17
    - Sharp, Malcolm, 1946-1948, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 838)
    - Shaughnessy, M. Quinn, 1949, 1951 (Box 69, Folder 839)
    - Shea, Francis M., 1942, 1947, 1953-1955 (Box 69, Folder 840)
    - Sheridan, Edward A., 1941-1943 (Box 69, Folder 841)
    - Shientag, Bernard L., 1942-1945 (Box 69, Folder 842)
    - Shulman, Harry, 1942, 1954-1955, n.d (Box 69, Folder 843)
    - Shuttleworth, Walter, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 844)
    - Siegel, Nathan, 1942 (Box 69, Folder 845)
    - Silberman, David B., 1942, 1945, 1951, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 846)
      See also: box 49, folder 168
    - Silving, Helen, 1947-1948, 1950-1957, undated (Box 69, Folder 847)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 28/12
    - Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1942-1947, 1949-1951, 1954-1956 (Box 69, Folder 848)
    - Simons, Charles C., 1945 (Box 69, Folder 849)
      See also: box 91, folder 742
    - Simons, Hans., 1941, 1946-1947, 1950-1951 (Box 69, Folder 850)
    - Simpson, Sidney Post, 1946-1948 (Box 69, Folder 851)
    - Slaff, George, 1950, undated (Box 69, Folder 852)
    - Smith, Hubert Winston, 1950 (Box 69, Folder 853)
    - Smith, Margaret Chase, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 854)
    - Smith, Walter ("Red"), 1951-1953 (Box 69, Folder 855)
    - Snyder, Orvill C., 1956 (Box 69, Folder 856)
    - Society for Ethical Culture, The., 1945-1946, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 857)
    - Solow, Herbert, 1942, 1948, 1950, 1952-1953, undated (Box 69, Folder 858)
    - Sommerich, Otto C. and Edith, 1942, 1944-1946, 1950-1951, 1953-1957 (Box 69, Folder 859)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 25-2/12
    - Sommers, Martin, 1942 (Box 69, Folder 860)
    - Sondel, Bess, 1944 (Box 69, Folder 861)
    - Sonnenberg, Benjamin, 1941-1945, 1947, 1949-1951, 1954-1956, undated (Box 69, Folder 862)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 14/14
    - Spaeth, Carl B., 1947, 1952, 1954 (Box 69, Folder 863)
    - Spivak, Lawrence E., 1945-1946, 1950 (Box 69, Folder 864)
    - Stanford Law Review, 1951, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 865)
    - Stansky, Lyman, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 866)
    - Starrs, John R., 1955 (Box 69, Folder 867)
    - State, United States Department of, 1952-1954, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 868)
    - Steinberg, Milton, 1945 (Box 70, Folder 869)
    - Steiner, Ralph, 1941-1942, undated (Box 70, Folder 870)
    - Stern, Harold H., 1943 (Box 70, Folder 871)
    - Stern, J. David, 1955 (Box 70, Folder 872)
    - Stern, William A., 1941, 1945, 1951-1952 (Box 70, Folder 873)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1948, 1952 (Box 70, Folder 874)
    - Stix, Thomas L., 1944-1947, 1949, 1953-1954, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 875)
    - Stone, Harlan F., 1941-1943, 1945 (Box 70, Folder 876)
    - Stone, Julius, 1948-1950 (Box 70, Folder 877)
    - Stone, Julius F. Jr., 1941, 1946 (Box 70, Folder 878)
    - Stone, Wilfred S., 1942 (Box 70, Folder 879)
    - Stout, Wesley Winans., 1941 (Box 70, Folder 880)
      See also: box 66, folder 761
    - Straight, Michael, 1942, 1947 (Box 70, Folder 881)
    - Straus, Roger W. Jr., 1947, 1949 (Box 70, Folder 882)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 12/2
    - Strauss, Helen, 1944-1956, undated (Box 70, Folder 883)
    - Stringham, Emerson, 1941, 1943 (Box 70, Folder 884)
    - Strong, Lydia, 1954 (Box 70, Folder 885)
    - Stryker, Lloyd Paul, 1945, 1952 (Box 70, Folder 886)
    - Sturgis, Wesley A., 1945-1949, 1951-1953 (Box 70, Folder 887)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 8/18
    - Sullivan, Harry Stack, 1941, 1945 (Box 70, Folder 888)
    - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays, 1942-1943 (Box 70, Folder 889)
    - Survey Associates, Inc., 1945-1946, 1950 (Box 70, Folder 890)
    - Swan, Thomas Walter., 1941-1955 (Box 70, Folder 891)
    - Swiren, Max, 1942, 1945-1947, 1949-1953 (Box 70, Folder 892)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 16/16
    - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1942, 1947-1948 (Box 70, Folder 893)
    - Syracuse Law Review, 1948-1949 (Box 70, Folder 894)
    - Syracuse University, 1947-1949 (Box 70, Folder 895)
    - T, 1941-1942, 1944-1948, 1950-1956 (Box 70, Folder 896)
    - Taggart, Leslie D., 1945 (Box 70, Folder 897)
    - Tanabe, Kohji, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 898)
    - Tarrasch, Hertha, 1950-1951 (Box 70, Folder 899)
    - Tead, Ordway, 1954 (Box 70, Folder 900)
    - Texas, University of, School of Law, 1944, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 901)
    - Thompson, Dorothy, 1942 (Box 70, Folder 902)
    - Thompson, Guy A., 1942 (Box 70, Folder 903)
    - Timberg, Sigmund, 1941, 1943, 1946, 1948, 1951, 1953, 1956, undated (Box 70, Folder 904)
    - Timbers, William H., 1953, 1955-1957 (Box 70, Folder 905)
    - Time, 1943, 1945-1946, 1948 (Box 70, Folder 906)
      See also: box 68, folder 824
    - Topkis, Jay H., 1953, 1956, undated (Box 70, Folder 907)
    - Town Hall, Inc., The, 1945, 1956 (Box 70, Folder 908)
    - Treasury Department, United States, 1941-1942, 1945, 1953-1954 (Box 70, Folder 909)
    - Truman, Harry S., 1945, 1947-1948, 1951 (Box 70, Folder 910)
    - Tugwell, Rexford Guy, 1945, 1948, 1952-1953 (Box 71, Folder 911)
    - Tweed, Harrison, 1945, 1948 (Box 71, Folder 912)
    - U, 1941-1942, 1947-1951 (Box 71, Folder 913)
    - United States government agencies, 1941-1954, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 914)
    - United World Federalists, Inc., 1947-1948 (Box 71, Folder 915)
    - Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 916)
    - V, 1941-1943, 1945, 1947-1951, 1955, undated (Box 71, Folder 917)
    - Vanderbilt Law Review, 1950-1952 (Box 71, Folder 918)
    - Van Doren, Irita, 1948-1949, 1952, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 919)
    - Viereck, Peter, 1951 (Box 71, Folder 920)
    - Vinson, Fred M., 1945-1946, 1950 (Box 71, Folder 921)
    - Virginia Law Review, 1942-1943, 1945, 1951-1952 (Box 71, Folder 922)
    - Virginia Law Weekly, 1948-1949, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 923)
    - W, 1941-1956, undated (Box 71, Folder 924)
    - Wagner, Robert F., 1956 (Box 71, Folder 925)
    - Wald, Robert Lewis and Patricia (McGowan), 1951-1953, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 926)
      Letters To JNF/ From JNF: 3-2/2
    - Wallace, Henry A., 1945-1946 (Box 71, Folder 927)
    - Wallach, Sidney, 1943, 1945, 1947, 1949 (Box 71, Folder 928)
    - Walsh, Lawrence E., 1956 (Box 71, Folder 929)
    - Warren, Earl, 1954, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 930)
    - The Washington Post, 1942, 1948-1949 (Box 71, Folder 931)
    - Washington, University of, School of Law, 1948, 1951, 1954 (Box 71, Folder 932)
    - Waterman, Sterry Robinson., 1955-1956, undated (Box 71, Folder 933)
    - Watkins, William R., 1942 (Box 71, Folder 934)
    - Webster, Bethuel M., 1943, 1945, 1948, 1952-1954 (Box 71, Folder 935)
    - Wechsler, Herbert, 1942, 1947, 1950-1951, 1956, undated (Box 71, Folder 936)
    - Wechsler, James, 1950, 1954, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 937)
    - Wehle, Louis B., 1947, 1949-1950 (Box 71, Folder 938)
    - Weil, Frank E. G., 1956 (Box 71, Folder 939)
    - Weiner, Joseph L., 1941, 1943-1946, 1948-1949, 1953-1954, 1956, undated (Box 71, Folder 940)
    - Weinfeld, Edward., 1951, 1953-1956 (Box 71, Folder 941)
    - Weiss, Paul, 1950-1956, undated (Box 71, Folder 942)
    - Welles, Sumner, 1944 (Box 71, Folder 943)
    - Wels, Richard H., 1947-1948, 1952, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 944)
    - West, Daniel W., 1949, 1955-1956 (Box 72, Folder 945)
    - West, Ranyard, 1949, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 946)
    - West, Rebecca, 1956, undated (Box 72, Folder 947)
    - Westervelt, W. I., 1946-1947 (Box 72, Folder 948)
    - White-Collar Justice: letters in response to an article written by JNF., 1943 (Box 72, Folder 949)
      See also: box 157, folder 458
    - White, Harry D., 1944-1945 (Box 72, Folder 950)
    - White, Leonard D., 1945-1946 (Box 72, Folder 951)
    - Wickard, Claude R., 1941-1942 (Box 72, Folder 952)
    - Wiener, Frederick Bernays, 1942-1944, 1948-1950, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 953)
    - Willcox, Bertram F., 1951, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 954)
    - William Alanson White Institute of Psychiatry, The, 1945, 1947-1951, 1955-1956 (Box 72, Folder 955)
    - William Morris Agency., 1944-1956, undated (Box 72, Folder 956)
      See also: box 70, folder 883
    - Williams, Glanville, 1945, 1952, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 957)
    - Williams, J. E. Hall, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 958)
    - Williams, Ross, 1945, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 959)
    - Wilson, Richard L., 1948 (Box 72, Folder 960)